This Privacy Policy describes how Shanghai Cuntu Technology Co.,Ltd. (“Cuntu”) handles personal information we collect about usersof our website at www.photovault.cn and our mobile applications(collectively, the “Service”).

Personal Information We Collect

Information You Give Us

We collect personal information you give us, such as:

Account information. We collect personal information when youcreate an account, such as your email address.

Account content. If you have purchased our Service, you can useand store photo and video data in the Service.

Transaction information. When you order paid versions of theService we collect information necessary to complete thetransaction, including your name, payment information and billinginformation.

Feedback and correspondence. You may share information withus when you respond to surveys, request customer support orotherwise interact with us.

Device data. You may choose to give us permission to accesscertain data on or components of your device, such as your photos,contacts, microphone and camera. You can always disable thisaccess in your device’s settings.

Sensitive personal information

We will never ask you to send us or submit to the Service anyinformation related to racial or ethnic origin; political opinions orunion membership; religious or other beliefs; your health, biometricor genetic information; information about your sexual preference orsexual orientation; or information about your criminal background.

Information we collect automatically

Device and usage information. We use server logs, cookies andsimilar technologies to automatically collect information about yourcomputer or device and how you interact with the Service. Forexample, we may record your application version, browser type,computer or mobile operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address(a number that is automatically assigned to your computer or mobiledevice when you use the Internet, which may vary from session tosession) and your unique device, application or advertisingidentifiers. In addition to information about your device, we collectinformation about how you interact with the Service, such as thepage that referred you, your search terms, pages or areas of theService you use or share, the time and duration of visits, featuresyou used and links you clicked on.

Advertising

If you use an ad-supported version of the Service, advertisingcompanies use cookies and similar technologies to collectinformation about how you use it, and to serve you ads tailored toyour interests in the Service and elsewhere.

How We Use Your Personal Information

We will only use your personal information in ways that arecompatible with the purposes listed below for which it was collectedor as subsequently authorized by you.

To provide the Service

We use your personal information to provide and support theService. As part of providing the Service we may send you serviceannouncements, technical notices, updates, security alerts andsupport-related messages through the Service or by email. We mayalso communicate with you in response to your support requests,questions or feedback.

For research and development

We use the information we collect to better understand yourinterests and the Service, make improvements to the Service and todevelop new features and services.

To create anonymous data

We may create aggregated and other anonymous data from ourusers’ personal information. We make personal information intoanonymous data by removing information that makes the datapersonally identifiable to you. We may use this anonymous data andshare it with third parties to operate, understand and improve ourService, develop new services and for other lawful businesspurposes.

For security, compliance, fraud prevention and safety

We may use your personal information as we believe appropriate toinvestigate or prevent violation of the law or our Terms of Service;to secure the Service; to protect our, your or others’ rights, privacy,safety or property; and to protect, investigate and deter againstfraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity.

For compliance with law; legal claims

We may use your personal information as we believe appropriate to(a) comply with applicable laws, lawful requests and legal process,such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from governmentauthorities, (b) where permitted by law in connection with a legalinvestigation and (c) to prosecute or defend legal claims

With your consent

In some cases we may ask for your consent to collect, use or shareyour personal information with your consent, such as when werequest access to your photos or other data through prompts in yourmobile operating system.

How We Share Your Personal Information

Affiliates

We may share some or all of your personal information with oursubsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under commoncontrol, in which case we will require those entities to honor thisPrivacy Policy.

Service providers

We may employ third party companies or individuals to provide servicesthat support the Service (such as customer support, hosting, paymentprocessing, website and mobile app analytics and email delivery). Weauthorize these service providers to use your personal information onlyas necessary in connection with providing their services to us. If we learnthat a service provider is using or disclosing personal information in amanner contrary to this Privacy Policy, we will take reasonable steps tostop it.

For compliance with law; legal claims; security, compliance,fraud prevention and safety

We may disclose information about you as we believe appropriate togovernment or law enforcement officials or private parties (a) forthe security, compliance, fraud prevention and safetypurposes described above; (b) as required by law, lawful requestsor legal process; (c) where permitted by law in connection with anylegal investigation; and (d) to prosecute or defend legal claims.

Business transfers

We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our business orassets, including your personal information, in connection with a businessdeal (or potential business deal) such as a merger, consolidation,acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

Your Choices

Access, correct or delete

If you have an account, you can access and update the personalinformation in your profile. Registered users may also contact us torequest deletion of your account and personal information. We may

request information from you to help us confirm your identity andprocess your request. Applicable law may require or permit us todecline your request, such as where we need to retain yourinformation for security, compliance, fraud prevention and safety, tocomply with law or for legal claims. If we decline your request, wewill tell you why, subject to legal restrictions. Once we processyour request you will not be able to access your account or use theService. When we delete any information, it will be deleted fromour active database, but where permitted by law, may remain for aperiod of time in our backup files or other instances where deletionis not practicable.

Security

We use a variety of industry-standard technologies and proceduresto help protect your personal information from unauthorized access,use, or disclosure. However, security risk is inherent in allinformation technology. Thus, while we use reasonable efforts toprotect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolutesecurity. If you believe the security of the Service or your personalinformation has been compromised, contact us immediately.

International Data Use

Shanghai Cuntu Technology Co., Ltd is headquartered in the China.Your personal information may be collected, used and stored inChina. Privacy laws in the locations where we handle your personalinformation may not be as protective as the privacy laws in yourhome country.

Third Party Sites and Services

The Service may link to or integrate with other websites andservices operated by third parties, including social media platforms,advertising services and other websites and applications. Theselinks and integrations are not endorsements of, or representationsthat we are affiliated with, any third party. We do not control thirdparty websites, applications or services and we are not responsible

for their actions. Third party websites and services follow differentrules regarding their collection, use and sharing of your personalinformation and we encourage you to read their privacy policies tolearn more.

Children

The Service is not directed to anyone under the age of 16. A parentor guardian who becomes aware that a child has used the Servicemay contact us and we will attempt to delete the child’s personalinformation as soon as possible.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make materialchanges to this Privacy Policy we will notify you by email (if we have youremail address) or another reasonable manner through the Service. Anymodifications to this Privacy Policy will be effective when posted (or asotherwise indicated at the time of posting).

If you object to an update of this Privacy Policy, you must notify us andask to deactivate your account and delete your personal information priorto the effective date of the update. Continued use of the Service after anupdate to this Privacy Policy will indicate your acceptance of the update.

Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy,please contact us at:

Shanghai Cuntu Technology Co., Ltd.1607, Tower B, Baodi Plaza, #588 Dalian RoadShanghai, 200082Chinaphotovault.info@gmail.com
